大家听好了  PJ的生日就是本周六了
Ok people, P.J.'s birthday is this Saturday.
大家每个人都要送他礼物
And everyone needs to buy him a present.
我说的大家  指的是盖比
And by everyone, I mean Gabe.
所说的“礼物” 指的是花钱买的
And by "buy him a present", she means actually purchase one.
不是借也不是去偷
Not borrow or steal it.
你们干吗都针对我  我一直都送PJ礼物的
Why are you guys peeking on me. I always get P.J. a present.
去年  你把他的衬衫稍微包装了一下  就又送给他了
Last year, you wrapped up one of his shirts and gave it to him.
而且他很喜欢
And he loved it.
不敢相信我大儿子都要十八了
I can't believe my baby boy is turning 18.
嘿  大家  聊什么呢
Hey guys, what're you talking about?
没什么
Nothing!
你没事吹什么口哨
What are you whistling about?
反正不是因为我的生日  这点可以肯定
Not my birthday. That's for sure.
嘿  PJ  你想要条裤子吗  跟你穿着的这条一模一样的
Hey P.J., how would you like a pair of pants exactly like those?
噢  天啊
Oh man!
泰迪  怎么了
Teddy. Are you ok?
一想起我要去亲斯宾塞  我就郁闷
I'm just bummed out that I have to kiss Spencer.
你前男友斯宾塞  背叛你的那个
Your ex-boyfriend Spencer? The one who cheated on you?
不是的  老爸  是我生命中的另一个斯宾塞
No, dad, the other Spencer in my life.
好吧  那你为什么要去亲他啊
Well, why would you want to kiss that guy?
因为我需要一辆车
Because I need a car.
说明白点  他糊涂了
Tell him more. He's lost.
好吧  我在冒险天地找了份新工作
Ok, I've got a new job at Super Adventure Land.
我要扮演公主  公主要去亲青蛙  而青蛙就是
I have to play the princess, princess has to kiss to frog and the frog is...
斯宾塞
Spencer.
亲爱的泰迪  我同情你啊
Teddy honey, I feel for you.
我知道去吻你的前任有多么的尴尬
I know how uncomfortable it is to kiss your ex.
我记着大学的时候有一次
I remember this one time in college...
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： WaitinZ
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第二十七集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E27  Can You Keep a Secret
查莉  你动爸爸的易拉罐了吗
Charlie. Did you do something with daddy's can.
没有  爸爸
No daddy.
那你看见它去哪了吗
Well did you see where it went?
这是个秘密
It's a secret.
好吧  那你能告诉爸爸这个秘密吗
Well, do you want to tell daddy the secret?
盖比
Gabe.
你真是我的掌中宝
That's why you are my favorite.
盖比  你是不是偷走了我的易拉罐
Gabe. Did you just steal my can.
易拉罐  我不知道你在说什么易拉罐
Can? I don't know anything about the can.
离柜子远点
Step away from the cabin.
不  不  老爸
No, no, dad.
-听话  -老爸  我不觉得你会愿意
-Come on.  -Dad, I really don't think you want to...
打开的
...do that.
搞什么
What's going on?
回收利用
I'm recycling.
-别开玩笑  -没开玩笑
-No kid. -Yeah.
我  我为环境所殚精竭虑
I'm... I'm concerned about the environment.
我可是要在地球上活上一段时间的
I'm gonna be on this planet for a really long time.
而你  你就不用为此担心
Now you, you've got nothing to worry about.
这么说来  对于回收利用的心血来潮
So, all this sudden interest in recycling
并非另有所图  比如
has nothing to do with the fact that maybe...
想从中捞取点儿小钱
you think you can make a little money off it.
哈  是吗
Ahh, is that right?
我不知道还能卖钱啊
I did not know that.
是吗  好像还有件事你不清楚
Well, here's something else you don't seem to know,
在科罗拉多州  回收铝罐是不会给你钱的
In the state of Colorado, they don't give you money for aluminum cans.
噢  是的  我知道
Oh, yeah, I knew that.
噢  老爸  帮个忙  能载我一程吗
Oh, dad, by the way, can you give me a ride?
好啊  去哪儿
Sure, where to?
堪萨斯州
Kansas.
嘿  老妈  你猜怎么着  我加入了西班牙俱乐部
Hey mom, guess what? I join Spanish club.
不会又是为了学校旅行或者约会小姑娘吧
Is it about taking a school trip or meeting girls.
是为了去旅行
It's about taking a trip...
和姑娘一起  用西语说就是  伴女
...with girls or as we say in Spanish: con-girls.
总之我需要去墨西哥的护照  所以需要我的出生证明
Anyway I may need a passport to go to Mexico so I need my birth certificate.
-你需要出生证明  -是啊  你有吧
-You need your birth certificate.  -Yes. You got it, right?
有啊
Yeah...
在
It's...
在我的文档里
It's in my files.
我会给你找出来的
I will take it out for you.
-谢了  -没什么  小意思
-Thanks.  -Yeah, no problem.
老鲍啊  纸包不住火啊
Bob, it finally happened.
PJ想要他的出生证明
P.J. wants to see his birth certificate.
就知道这天会到来的
We knew this day would come.
噢  别哭哭啼啼的  爷们儿点儿
Oh, stop whimpering and man up!
嘿
Hey!
Hey.
看来  今天要上演吻戏了  对吧
So, today is the... day of the big kiss. Huh?
是啊  看来如此
Yeah, it's so.
你看起来美极了  穿上这套服装
You look great... in that outfit.
噢  我知道  我是说谢谢
Oh, I know. I mean thanks.
听着  斯宾塞  咱们没理由这么尴尬
Look! Spencer, there is no reason why it has to be awkward.
其实  并不是咱俩亲
Well... It's not you and I kissing.
是咱俩的角色亲  咱俩都是专业演员  是吧
It's just our characters. I mean we're professionals. Right?
没错  我是个专业演员  穿着
You are right. I'm as professional as a guy in...
青蛙服挣着底薪的专业演员
frog suit making minimum wage it can be.
好了  该我们了
Well, that's our cue.
外面见
See you out there.
在这段快乐的舞蹈结束之时
And when their joyous dance came to an end.
王子和公主献上了他们的爱情之吻
The prince and the princess seal their love with a kiss.
等等  泰迪
Wait, Teddy.
王子和公主携手迈向了幸福快乐的生活
And the prince and the princess walk off together and live happily ever after.
老鲍啊  你有十八年的时间去更改PJ的出生证明
Bob, you had 18 years to change P.J.'s birth certificate.
为什么不去啊
Why didn't you?
就这一次  咱们能别互相抱怨吗
For once, can we not play the blaming game.
咱们除了抱怨还能干什么
It's the only game we know.
好了  听着  现在有一个非常简单的解决方法
Ok, look. There is a... there is a very simple solution.
我们告诉PJ咱们支付不起去墨西哥的费用
We'll just tell P.J. we can't afford to send him to Mexico.
你让我向他撒谎
You want me to lie to him?
就这么定了
I'm in.
家父好  家母好
Hola padre. Hola madre.
邓肯先生  邓肯夫人好
Hola Sr. and Sra. Duncan.
埃米特  你好啊
Hola Emmett. Cómo estás?
她说的是啥
What's she saying?
我哪知道
I have no idea.
PJ  嘿  听着
P.J., hey. Eh, listen.
听着  关于你的旅行  有个不好的消息
Look, we've got some bad news about the trip
考虑到你的西语学得这么好  经过痛苦的抉择
which is heartbreaking considering how well you're doing with the Spanish.
儿子  我们支付不起你去墨西哥的费用  抱歉
Honey. We can't afford to pay for your trip to Mexico. I'm so sorry.
其实  西班牙俱乐部全年集资善款
Actually, the Spanish club is having fund raised all year.
就是为了这次郊游
The trip is paid for.
没错  分文不掏到我们北边的邻居那儿玩一圈
Yeah. no cost of a dime, it's a free trip to our neighbour to the north.
是南边
It's... south.
嗯  回来的时候不就得朝北走么
Umm, not on the way back.
斯宾塞
Spencer.
嘿  呃  能谈谈吗
Hey, eh. Can we talk?
我  我只是想看看你还好吗
I eh, just want to make sure you are ok.
我不好
Well I'm not ok.
泰迪  我感觉很糟
Teddy, I felt terrible about this, alright?
是你先接手的这份工作
You are in the job first
如果吻戏让你感觉很糟糕  那我还是辞职吧
and kissing me makes you feel that bad then I'm just going to quit.
不是的  斯宾塞  不是那个吻糟糕  而是那个吻
No, Spencer. It's not that the kiss was bad. It's the kiss was...
很好
Good.
噢
Ohh.
知道吗  我并不  我并不希望它很好
You know. I didn't... I didn't want it to be good.
事实上  我以为它很恶心  所以做好了各种准备
In fact, I was all prepared to be disgusted.
谢了
Thanks.
现在我不知所措了
Now I don't know what to do.
泰迪
Teddy...
我所做过最愚蠢的事情就是伤害你
Hurting you was the stupidest thing I've did.
能再给我一次机会吗
Could you please give me another chance?
你注意到了吗  每次我们接吻  气球都会冒出来
Did you notice that every time we kiss balloons appear?
还好有气球挡着
It was good to see them too.
来吧  查莉  说啊
Come on Charllie, say it.
我爱你
I love you!
够萌吧  奶奶
Isn't that adorable, grandma?
是啊  她让我给您打电话就是为了对您说这句话
Yes, she made me call just so she could tell you that.
奶奶听我说  在与您聊天之际  我突然有个想法
Hey listen, grandma. While I got you on the horn a thought occured to me.
每年您都会送给我一份五十块的圣诞红包
Every year you send me a Christmas check for 50$.
您猜怎么着  我仔细想了想
And you know what? I'm thinking about it.
如果您把未来十年的红包一次性支付了  会不会简单些呢
Won't it be easier for you to send me the next 10 checks for all at once?
就好像  就像预付一样
You know, like a prepay plan.
-盖比  -我先挂了
-Gabe!  -Got to go.
好了  老实交代
Ok, out with it.
你想拿这钱干什么
What do you try to get this money for?
好吧
Alright.
事实就是我想要Z方六代
The truth is I want the ZCube 6.
新款游戏系统  我去年才给你买的Z方五代
A new game system? I just got you the ZCube 5 last year.
是啊  去年
Yeah, last year!
连3D图像都不支持  我视它为鸡肋
It doesn't even have 3D graphics. I might have used it as a food store.
好吧  那你给我另辟蹊径赚钱去
Ok, you are gonna have to find another way to make money
别再搜刮你的亲戚了
without shaking down your relatives.
您好
Hello.
噢  嘿  黛安姑妈
Oh, hey Aunt Diane.
是啊  谢谢给我回电
Yeah, thanks for calling back.
噢  我打电话有事吗
Oh, what did I want?
呃  就是  就是说句  我爱你
Eh, eh just... just say I... I love ya.
看看你把我逼的
See what you're making me do.
呃  PJ  我要向你坦白点事情
Eh, P.J.. There is something I need to tell you.
在我张嘴之前
Now before I say anything,
我想让你清楚  你妈和我会非常非常爱你的
I just want you to know your mother and I would love you very much.
听着不对劲啊  怎么了
That doesn't sound good. What's going on?
PJ  我们向你隐瞒了一个秘密
P.J., we've been keeping a secret from you.
-什么秘密  -关于你的姓名
-What is it?  -It's about your name.
如你所知  你的名字由你的曾祖父帕特里克·约翰而得
As you know, you were named after your great grandfather Patrick John.
没错  他们还经常叫我帕蒂·约翰
Yeah, they gave and usually called me Patty John.
没错  没错  好了  接下来是你所不知的
Yeah, yeah, ok, here is what you don't know.
呃  你出生的时候
Uhm, when you were born,
我填写了这份证明  而且我是相当的紧张
I filled out the papers and I was really nervous and...
我我我觉着我的手微微地颤抖了一下  给你
I-I-I think my hand was shaking a little and here.
这才是你的合法出生证明
That is your legal birth certificate.
这才是PJ的意思吗
That's what P.J. stands for.
恐怕是的
I'm afraid so.
我叫珀蒂·约翰
My name is Potty John.
法律上  是的
Legally, yes!
珀蒂·约翰
Potty John.
我以两个厕所而得名
I'm named after two toilets.
（注：Potty有婴儿马桶的意思  John有厕所的意思）
法律上  是的
Legally, yeah!
而你从没想过改一下吗
And you never bother to fix this.
我们一直都在想着改
But we always meant to.
我只是  我们一直没时间啊
I just, we just never got around to it.
有点像楼上的马桶  是吧
Kinda like the upstairs potty huh?
不该这么早告诉你是吧
Too soon?
我和你爸谈了谈
So your dad and I were talking and...
对于你每天都去工作感到很过意不去
we felt really bad that you have to go to work every day
还要去亲那个可恶的斯宾塞
and kiss that horrible Spencer.
是吗 “可恶”这个词有点言重了
Yeah. "Horrible" is kinda a strong word.
总之  鉴于你这么做的唯一目的就是为了挣钱买车
Anyway, since the only reason you're doing this is to get money for a car.
那好
Well...
跟我来
Come with me.
看啊
Tada!
-噢  这是啥  -你的新车喽
-Ooh. What's this?  -It's your new car.
不会吧
Shut up!
有个护士想卖了它  我看价钱不错就将它拿下了
One of the other nurses was selling it and I got a great price.
现在归你了
Now it's all yours.
噢  我不知道该说什么了  谢谢  谢谢
Aww! I don't know what to say. Thank you thank you...
上车吧
Get in.
更让人高兴的是  你可以辞去工作
And the best part is now you can quit your job
然后远离那个混帐斯宾塞十万八千里了
so that you never have to go near that jerk Spencer ever again.
耶
Yay.
你应该给这辆车起个名字
You should give it a name.
噢  我知道了  就叫“不用再亲斯宾塞号”
Oh I know. How about the "Now I don't have to kiss Spencer anymore mobile"?
或者叫艾德  我比较中意艾德
Or Ed. I kinda like Ed.
进来吧  大家  这边请
Come on in guys. Right this way.
娱乐马上开始
The fun begins in a minute.
-呃  盖比  -咋了
-Err, Gabe.  -Yep.
这帮孩子是谁呀  我之前没见过啊
Who're these kids. I've never seen them before.
之所以没见过
You've never seen them
是因为这帮孩子从未被邀请过去任何地方
because these are the kids who never get invited anywhere.
好吧  那他们怎么来咱家了  你有何企图
Ok, so why are they here. What's in it for you.
给这些宅男送去欢乐从而带给我的满足感
The satisfaction of bringing joy to a few sad misfits.
打扰一下
Excuse me!
怎么了
Yes!
我是应该现在给你二十块还是等游戏结束之后
Do I give you the twenty dollars now or when the play date is over?
-现在就可以  -好的
-Now is good.  -Awesome.
盖比
Gabe.
你看见那顽皮小家伙的脸上挂着的微笑了吗
Did you see the smile on the little scamp's face.
老妈  我昨天做了个超疯狂的梦
Mom, I had the craziest dream last night.
噢  我也是
Ooh, me too.
我梦见我在高中
I was in high school.
唯独我有双翅膀  然后所有啦啦队员都羡慕嫉妒恨
Only I had wings and all the cheerleaders were really jealous
因为在排练动作的时候我可以一直飞着
because I kept flying around during our routine.
然后不知打哪雷迪·嘎嘎冒出来了  还朝我扔鞋
Then out of nowhere, Lady Gaga appeares throwing her shoe at me.
好了  老妈  能谈谈我的梦吗
Ok mom, can we stay on me.
话说回来  在我的疯狂一梦中
Anyway, in my crazy dream,
斯宾塞和我重归于好了
Spencer and I got back together.
然后你们发现了  就没收了我的车
And then you guys found out and you took my car away.
是吗
Oh duh.
知道吗  泰迪  还是我的梦更好玩些
You know Teddy, my dream is a lot more entertaining than yours.
老妈  我和你说点事
Mom, I have to tell you something.
你知道这辆车有卫星电台吗
Did you know that this car has a satellite radio?
-真的  -当然
-It does?  -Uh-huh.
一百多个电台
Over 100 stations.
你刚才想说啥
You were saying?
好了  好了  听着  事情是这样的  我
Right, right, ok. Here is the thing. I...
那个是MP3插口吗
Is that the mp3 hookup?
这辆车就是变形金刚啊
This baby is fully loaded.
噢  天啊  你真让我左右为难了
Oh men. You are not making this easier.
说到不再为难  看看  你自己的加油卡
Speaking of making things easier, ba-bam, your very own gas card.
哈
Huh.
还有  避免你迷路  看看  你的GPS
And, so you don't get lost. Ba-bam, your very own GPS.
你刚才想和我说什么
Now what was that you wanted to tell me?
妈啊  我想告诉你  我已经深深地爱上了
Mom, I want to tell you that I'm in love...
艾德
...with Ed.
好了  这是盖比送的
Alright, this is from Gabe.
一张价值十块钱的冰冻酸奶礼券
A 10-dollar gift card for frozen yogurt.
可能还剩六块了
Probably about 6 dollars left on it.
我当时有点饿了
I was feeling snacky!
好了  这是我的
Ok, here is mine.
是个日记本  为你去墨西哥所准备的
It's a journal for your trip to Mexico.
每天写一写你的所做  所闻  还有心里的感受
Everyday you can write what you did, what you saw, how you felt about it.
-啊  我喜欢  -那就好
-Aw, I love it.  -Yeah.
你是不是真不知道什么礼物适合我啊You'll never get a gift secret for decision?
不知道
No.
好了  这是我和你爸送给你的
Okay. Here is a little something from mom and dad.
噢  哇  你们太慷慨大方了
Oh, wow, guys. This is so generous.
只是给你墨西哥之行的一点儿零花钱
Just a little spending money for Mexico.
享受你的晚餐吧
Enjoy your dinaro.
噢  难道我只能把路费花在晚餐上吗
Oh, do I have to spend it on dinaro.
可以用来吃早饭和午饭吗
Can I use it for breakfast-o or lunch-o?
儿子  等你到那儿之后  跟紧了老师
Sweetie, when you're down there, stay close to the teacher.
还有样东西要给你
There is one more thing we got you.
我今早直奔法院
Went down to the court house this morning.
终于把你的出生证明改好了
Finally got your birth certificate fixed.
你现在是名正言顺的PJ·邓肯了
You are now officially P.J. Duncan.
老爸啊  你复查这个了吗
Dad, did you double check this.
没有  怎么了  怎么有可能弄错PJ
No! Why, how can anybody possibly mess up P.J..
别问我  根据这张纸  我叫PP·邓肯
Don't ask me. According to this my name is PP Duncan.
起码不如原来那么难看了  对吧
Turn out, it's not looking so bad now, is it?
好了  看来大家的礼物都齐了  PP  生日快乐
Well, looks like that's all the presents. PP, happy birthday!!
噢  等等  还有一个  上面写着是查莉送的
Oh wait, wait. There's one left. It says it's from Charlie.
查莉  你不用给我买任何礼物的
Charlie! You don't have to give me anything.
什么  一把新吉他
What? A new guitar!
这正是我想要的  你们怎么知道的
This is just what I wanted. How do you guys know?
你买的吗
Did you do that?
啊  太棒了
Awww. It's so cool.
嘿  盖比
Hey Gabe.
你喜欢那个新款Z方吗
How are you liking that new ZCube?
噢  我不打算买了  因为Z方七代就要面世了
Oh, I decided not to get it, the ZCube 7's coming out soon.
你用那笔钱买了把吉他送给你老哥了
You used that money to buy that new guitar for your bro.
我不知道你在说些什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
噢  别装了  盖比
Oh come on Gabe.
如果你把这事告诉别人  我是不会原谅你的
If you tell anybody about this I will never forgive you.
你为啥想把这事儿当成秘密呢
Why would you want to keep that a secret?
因为
Because...
我不想让别人认为我这么娘  或者我关心我哥
I can't let people think that I've gone soft or that I love my brother.
好吧  好吧  我会保守这个秘密的
Alright alright. Your secret is safe with me.
我以你为荣  真是个乖宝宝
I'm proud of you. You're a good kid.
看  这正是我害怕谈到的
See! That's the exact kind of talk I was afraid of.
嘿  爸妈
Hey guys.
-嘿  -嗨  宝贝
-Hey.  -Hi honey.
这是车钥匙  我还回来了
There are the keys dad. I'm giving 'em back.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
因为反正你们都要主动没收的
Oh because you're gonna taking him back anyway.
我们为什么会没收
Why would we do that?
因为我有个秘密瞒着你们俩
There is a secret that I've been keeping from you guys.
进来吧
Come on in.
嗨  邓肯夫妇
Hi Mr. and Mrs. Duncan.
我和斯宾塞又恋上了
Spencer and I are dating again.
好吧  起初我没想告诉你们
Ok, at first I didn't want to tell you guys
是因为我怕你们会把车没收
because I was afraid that you would take away the car.
我知道我有两个选择  一是艾德
I figured that I had a choice to make either Ed
二是斯宾塞  所以在我长时间的思考之后
or Spencer so after thinking about it for a long time.
非常长的时间
A really long time.
我选择斯宾塞
I chose Spencer.
我决定再给他一次机会
I decided to give him another chance.
所以  我们和好了  而且我很快乐
So, we're back together now and I'm very happy.
好了  很高兴你能和我们坦诚相待
Well. I'm just glad that you could be honest with us.
而且  如果你能够快乐  那才是最重要的
And. If you're happy I guess that's all that really matter.
谢谢
Thanks.
你们让我继续留着这辆车
You're letting me keep the car.
我们让你为这辆车买单
We're letting you pay for the car.
那份工作你得继续干下去
With the job that you're going to keep.
可以
Fair enough.
邓肯家欢迎你  斯宾塞
Welcome back to the family Spencer.
如果你胆敢
And if you ever...
再次伤害我闺女
hurt my little girl again...
等死吧
Ba-Bam.
嘿  查莉  听好了  重大新闻
Hey Charlie, so, big news.
这周我得到了一个新的老男朋友  叫斯宾塞
This week I got a new old boyfriend named Spencer
还有一辆老的新车  叫艾德
and an old new car named Ed.
如果我对它爱护有加  也许有一天你就可以接手
And someday if I take good care of him, you could have him.
是艾德  不是斯宾塞  不然就怪怪的了
Oh Ed, not Spencer. That would be just weird.
打扰一下
Excuse me!
你是哪位
Who are you?
我是埃利奥特
I'm Eliot.
我付钱给盖比  可以再玩一回合捉迷藏
I paid Gabe for another play date for playing hide and seek.
但是我都躲起来快五个小时了
But I've been hiding for almost 5 hours.
他去练棒球了
He went to baseball practice.
噢  我等他
Oh, I'll wait.
言归正传  现在就剩一句了
Well, I guess there's only one thing left to say.
噢  嘿  你在啊  你来说这最后一句吧
Oh hey, you are here why don't you say it?
好运查莉
Good luck Charlie.
泰迪
Teddy!
谁说话呢
Who said that?
是我  你的车
It's me, your car.
艾德  你能说话
Ed, you can talk?
我更喜欢被称为艾德华
I prefer Edward.
没错  是我
And yes.
哈  这么说来你真是变形金刚了
Huh, so I have a talking car?
是不是意味着咱们可以并肩作战  除恶扬善
Oh does that mean we're going on an adventure and solve crimes and stuff.
这个嘛  听起来挺危险的
Well, that sounds kind of dangerous
我觉着咱们应该安全驾驶  不超速
I've thought we'd just drive carefully and stay within speed limit and stuff.
天哪  我的这辆变形金刚真是无聊啊
Oh man. So I have a talking car who's boring.
噢  还有件事忘了和你说了  我感觉不舒服
Oh uh, one other thing I have to tell you. I don't feel so good.
艾德华  艾德华说话啊
Edward, Edward talk to me.
吓你的
Gotcha.
现在我不无聊了吧
Not so boring now, am I?